DAVID WATTS

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT INFORMATION

Brisbane, QLD Australia

in LinkedIn: @davidwatts11

Github: <u>edaviddigital</u>

davdwatts11egmail.com
0412 957 215

EDUCATION

Coder Academy

DIPLOMA OF IT, 2022 (EXPECTED)

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology UNDERGRADUATE CERTIFICATE COMPUTER SCIENCE, 2020

Queensland University of Technology

GRADUATE DIPLOMA APPLIED FINANCE, 2015

Swinburne University

GRADUATE CERTIFICATE SCIENCE (NETWORK SYSTEMS), 2011

Griffith University

BACHELOR BUSINESS (INFORMATION SYSTEMS), ACADEMIC EXCELLENCE, 2010

SUMMARY

Emerging software engineer with previous experience in software development teams as a Business Analyst. Started a career change in 2020 by completing an Undergraduate Certificate in Computer Science, followed by a full stack web development course/bootcamp in 2021.

EXPERIENCE

Personal Projects

DWATTS.COM.AU 2020 - 2021

- <u>SolarMapper</u> Developing a two-sided marketplace using Ruby on Rails & PostgreSQL, deployed using Heroku
- <u>Solar App</u> Developed a command line app using Ruby for generating costs and benefits of solar systems
- <u>Portfolio</u> Used Sass/HTML to develop a responsive portfolio page, deployed using Netlify
- House Prices a regression model using Python & Jupyter Notebooks for predicting house sale prices

Lead Business Analyst

|VVY

MAY 2019 - MAR 2021

Documented and designed new features for a web application and event marketplace (<u>ivvy.com</u>)

Marketing Automation Manager

VILLAGE ROADSHOW OCT 2018 - MAY 2019

 Implemented systems & automated email/SMS journeys utilising Salesforce marketing cloud





DAVID WATTS

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFORMATION

- Brisbane, QLD Australia
- in LinkedIn: edavidwatts11
- Github: <u>edaviddigital</u>
- davdwattsllegmail.com 0412 957 215

WORK EXPERIENCE CONT.

Lead Business Analyst

COMPLY ADVANTAGE FEB 2017 - NOV 2017

- Implemented systems (Salesforce CRM & marketing)
- Lead a team of analysts supporting development of a financial services web application

Digital Business Analyst / Project Manager

MANTRA GROUP
JAN 2016 - OCT 2016

- Documented and designed a new website / accommodation booking engine
- Implemented email marketing and survey systems

Graduate to Senior Business Analyst

TELSTRA FEB 2010 - DEC 2015

- Worked in multiple teams as part of Telstra's technology graduate program, including network planning, commercial analysis, project management, strategy and operations
- Performed analysis for multiple network & IT projects, developing business cases & financial models



